{
    "subject": "resource/Eugenio_Barba",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Brindisi",
    "human_readable": "Eugenio Barba was born in Brindisi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7905825972557068,
            "question": "Where was Eugenio Barba born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.740374743938446,
            "question": "In what year was Eugenio Barba born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5194030404090881,
            "question": "Which country was Brindisi located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4830135405063629,
            "question": "What is Eugenio Barba known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3899499475955963,
            "question": "Name a notable work by Eugenio Barba."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38240301609039307,
            "question": "Where did Eugenio Barba live?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3710300624370575,
            "question": "Who were some of Eugenio Barba's contemporaries?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3075048625469208,
            "question": "What field is Eugenio Barba associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16548824310302734,
            "question": "How has Eugenio Barba influenced contemporary theatre?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1564416140317917,
            "question": "What are some of the key themes explored in Eugenio Barba's work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Eugenio Barba was born in Brindisi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4041_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has Eugenio Barba influenced contemporary theatre?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4041_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What field is Eugenio Barba associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4041_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who were some of Eugenio Barba's contemporaries?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4041_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_113.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_94.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4041_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in the form of a structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The first document mentions that Eugenio Barba was \"born in Brindisi, Italy\" and the other documents also mention his birthplace as being in Brindisi or Puglia (which is a region where Brindisi is located)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}